<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jetson Nano on Andrylat: Dev notes</title><link>https://aicurious.io/tags/jetson-nano/</link><description>Recent content in Jetson Nano on Andrylat: Dev notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2020-2021, Andrii Latyshev; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicurious.io/tags/jetson-nano/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advanced driver-assistance system on Jetson Nano Part 3 - Deep neural networks</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/adas-jetson-nano-deep-neural-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/adas-jetson-nano-deep-neural-networks/</guid><description>Recently, I have built a prototype of an advanced driver-assistance system (ADAS) using a Jetson Nano computer. In this project, I have successfully deployed 3 deep neural networks and some computer vision algorithms on a super cheap hardware of Jetson Nano. In the last two posts, I have introduced the system in hardware and software design. In this week, I write about two machine learning modules: Object Detection Module and Lane Detection Module.</description></item><item><title>Advanced driver-assistance system on Jetson Nano Part 2 - Software design</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/adas-jetson-nano-software/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/adas-jetson-nano-software/</guid><description>Recently, I have built a prototype of an advanced driver-assistance system (ADAS) using a Jetson Nano computer. In this project, I have successfully deployed 3 deep neural networks and some computer vision algorithms on a super cheap hardware of Jetson Nano. I decided to write this post series to share about how this system was designed and implemented. The first post is an introduction and the hardware design of my system.</description></item><item><title>Advanced driver-assistance system on Jetson Nano Part 1 - Intro &amp; Hardware design</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/adas-jetson-nano-intro-and-hardware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/adas-jetson-nano-intro-and-hardware/</guid><description>Recently, I have built a prototype of an advanced driver-assistance system (ADAS) using a Jetson Nano computer. In this project, I have successfully deployed 3 deep neural networks and some computer vision algorithms on a super cheap hardware of Jetson Nano. I decided to write this post series to share about how this system was designed and implemented. In this series, I will introduce the overall design of the system, 3 deep neural networks I used for environment analysis and some tutorials on TensorRT - the core technology to optimize neural networks for NVIDIA's system.</description></item></channel></rss>