<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Apollo on Andrylat: Dev notes</title><link>https://aicurious.io/tags/apollo/</link><description>Recent content in Apollo on Andrylat: Dev notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2020-2021, Andrii Latyshev; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicurious.io/tags/apollo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[MOOC] Apollo Lessons on Self-Driving Cars</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lessons-intro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lessons-intro/</guid><description>This is an introduction course to self-driving cars and Apollo platform - The Android of Self-Driving Car. Through this course, you will be able to identify key parts of self-driving cars and get to know Apollo architecture. You will be able to utilize Apollo HD Map, localization, perception, prediction, planning and control, and start the learning path of building a self-driving car.
My notes for this course:
Lecture 1: SCD Fundamentals Lecture 2: HD Maps Lecture 3: Localization Lecture 4: Perception Lecture 5: Prediction Lecture 6: Planning Lecture 7: Control</description></item><item><title>[MOOC] Apollo Lesson 3: Localization</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lesson-3-localization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lesson-3-localization/</guid><description>This is my note for lesson 3 of MOOC course: Self-Driving Fundamentals - Featuring Apollo. Content: How the vehicle localizes itself with a single-digit-centimeter-level accuracy.
Localization methods in Apollo The RTK (Real Time Kinematic) based method which incorporates GPS and IMU (Inertial Measurement Unit) information. The multi-sensor fusion method which incorporates GPS, IMU, and LiDAR information. Inertial navigation Global Navigation Satellite System (GNSS) Global Navigation Satellite System (GNSS) refers to a constellation of satellites providing signals from space that transmit positioning and timing data to GNSS receivers.</description></item><item><title>[MOOC] Apollo Lesson 2: HD Maps</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lesson-2-hd-maps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lesson-2-hd-maps/</guid><description>This is my note for lesson 2 of MOOC course: Self-Driving Fundamentals - Featuring Apollo. Content: High Definition maps for self driving cars.
HD Maps have a high precision and contain a lot of information than your ordinary map on smartphone, such as lane line markings, 3D representation of the road network, traffic signs... You can what you see and GPS to locate your self in the world and identify other objects.</description></item><item><title>[MOOC] Apollo Lesson 1: SDC Fundamentals</title><link>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lesson-1-fundamentals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aicurious.io/posts/apollo-sdc-lesson-1-fundamentals/</guid><description>This is my note for lesson 1 of MOOC course: Self-Driving Fundamentals - Featuring Apollo. Content: Identify the key parts of self-driving cars. The Apollo team and architecture.
Human vs Self-driving Car Human Self-Driving Car High traffic accident rate More reliable driving Learn to drive from scratch Learnable driving system Parking trouble No parking trouble Six levels of self-driving car Level 0: Base level - No autonomous task</description></item></channel></rss>